(Bernadette:)Thanks again for cooking.
(Amy:)Yeah, everything was delicious.
(Raj:)Well, I couldn't have done it
without my two favourite girls.
(Raj:)Martha Stewart and Rachael Ray.
(Mike:)Hey, Sheldon,
what do you say we go outside
(Mike:)and throw around the old pigskin?
(Sheldon:)This is a Jewish house.
(Sheldon:)I don't think they have pigskin.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Did someone say pigskin?
(Penny:)Hey, I'm sorry about today.
(Penny:)And I promise,
next time I get married,
(Penny:)it won't be a joke.
(Penny:)It'll be for love.
(Penny:)Or money.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, too.
(Bernadette:)Don't be.
It's my fault.
(Zack:)I was a terrible husband.
(Zack:)I was never around.
(Mike:)I know I'm hard on you,
(Mike:)but you're not the worst
son-in-law in the world.
(Howard:)Mike, that's the nicest thing
you've ever said to me.
(Mike:)Well, I'm drunk.
(Sheldon:)I just vomited on a lot of clowns.